[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Ben Wedeman, can you hear me?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "Wedeman", ",", "can", "you", "hear", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Yes, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Wedeman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moammar Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "What is going on there right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "there", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, at the moment, I think people are really bracing for the possibility that certainly after hearing that rather incoherent but threatening speech from Libyan leader Moammar Gadhafi that he may be trying to launch some sort of counteroffensive against the eastern part of the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "I", "think", "people", "are", "really", "bracing", "for", "the", "possibility", "that", "certainly", "after", "hearing", "that", "rather", "incoherent", "but", "threatening", "speech", "from", "Libyan", "leader", "Moammar", "Gadhafi", "that", "he", "may", "be", "trying", "to", "launch", "some", "sort", "of", "counteroffensive", "against", "the", "eastern", "part", "of", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Do you think -- do they believe, as the Egyptian people believed, that they can actually get rid of Gadhafi finally?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "--", "do", "they", "believe", ",", "as", "the", "Egyptian", "people", "believed", ",", "that", "they", "can", "actually", "get", "rid", "of", "Gadhafi", "finally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, I think they do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What's he potentially able to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "potentially", "able", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, he still has a fairly sizable air force.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "still", "has", "a", "fairly", "sizable", "air", "force", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What do you like to be called?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "like", "to", "be", "called", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Hef.", "answer_tokens": ["Hef", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What do you make of what we're seeing now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "we", "'re", "seeing", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Very exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "And you Tweet, of course?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "Tweet", ",", "of", "course", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "But it's fascinating to see so many of these young people in the Middle East taking on these old dictators and bringing them down through sheer force of, we want change, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "fascinating", "to", "see", "so", "many", "of", "these", "young", "people", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "taking", "on", "these", "old", "dictators", "and", "bringing", "them", "down", "through", "sheer", "force", "of", ",", "we", "want", "change", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, it is the purest form of democracy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "the", "purest", "form", "of", "democracy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Do you think it's the end of these old kind of dictatorial ruling families around the world who are fleecing their own people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "the", "end", "of", "these", "old", "kind", "of", "dictatorial", "ruling", "families", "around", "the", "world", "who", "are", "fleecing", "their", "own", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I think it will be -- you know, I don't think there's a simple answer to that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "simple", "answer", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "What's the answer for America, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "for", "America", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I think we need to get back to fundamentals in terms of -- you know, both conceptually and economically.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "need", "to", "get", "back", "to", "fundamentals", "in", "terms", "of", "--", "you", "know", ",", "both", "conceptually", "and", "economically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What's back to basics?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "back", "to", "basics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, one of the things I would be thinking about -- I mean what's happened, of course, is that we've outsourced half of our businesses, and national boundaries don't have a lot of meaning anymore.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "I", "would", "be", "thinking", "about", "--", "I", "mean", "what", "'s", "happened", ",", "of", "course", ",", "is", "that", "we", "'ve", "outsourced", "half", "of", "our", "businesses", ",", "and", "national", "boundaries", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "meaning", "anymore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "There's no future in that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "future", "in", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "\"Playboy\" sells around the world, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Playboy", "''", "sells", "around", "the", "world", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you have any sales in places like China at the moment or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "sales", "in", "places", "like", "China", "at", "the", "moment", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "We are one of the most famous brand in China.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "one", "of", "the", "most", "famous", "brand", "in", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "On the mainland of China where the magazine is not yet permitted, we are one of the most famous menswear brands.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "the", "mainland", "of", "China", "where", "the", "magazine", "is", "not", "yet", "permitted", ",", "we", "are", "one", "of", "the", "most", "famous", "menswear", "brands", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "So you sell the merchandise, but you can't sell the magazine?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "sell", "the", "merchandise", ",", "but", "you", "ca", "n't", "sell", "the", "magazine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "It can't be long before \"Playboy\" is allowed to be on sale?", "question_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "be", "long", "before", "``", "Playboy", "''", "is", "allowed", "to", "be", "on", "sale", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What's the fast way that Obama can try and sort this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "fast", "way", "that", "Obama", "can", "try", "and", "sort", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Man, you're asking the wrong guy in terms of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", ",", "you", "'re", "asking", "the", "wrong", "guy", "in", "terms", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Do you think it's forgotten what it did so magnificently 40, 50 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "forgotten", "what", "it", "did", "so", "magnificently", "40", ",", "50", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, not only do we need to put people to work, we need to become more sophisticated in terms of technology.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "only", "do", "we", "need", "to", "put", "people", "to", "work", ",", "we", "need", "to", "become", "more", "sophisticated", "in", "terms", "of", "technology", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "How excited do you sound in that video?", "question_tokens": ["How", "excited", "do", "you", "sound", "in", "that", "video", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "That was fun.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Hef, what do you possibly see in Crystal?", "question_tokens": ["Hef", ",", "what", "do", "you", "possibly", "see", "in", "Crystal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Yes --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What indeed?", "question_tokens": ["What", "indeed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Can I see the ring?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "see", "the", "ring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Here's the ring.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "ring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "You could have had any woman in the world -- you've had most of them, so how did you -- how did you narrow it down to Crystal?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "have", "had", "any", "woman", "in", "the", "world", "--", "you", "'ve", "had", "most", "of", "them", ",", "so", "how", "did", "you", "--", "how", "did", "you", "narrow", "it", "down", "to", "Crystal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, I've just -- just literally, you know, it's fate, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "just", "--", "just", "literally", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "fate", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "You're going to reveal the date of the wedding?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "reveal", "the", "date", "of", "the", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "The date of the wedding.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "date", "of", "the", "wedding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Can I tell him?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "tell", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "And how did you propose, Hef?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "did", "you", "propose", ",", "Hef", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, it was on Christmas Eve.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "on", "Christmas", "Eve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hef"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What's the magic of Hugh Hefner?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "magic", "of", "Hugh", "Hefner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I love Hef.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Hef", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Hefner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho Marx"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How long does the average marriage last?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "does", "the", "average", "marriage", "last", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Groucho Marx I think said, you're only as old as the woman you feel.", "answer_tokens": ["Groucho", "Marx", "I", "think", "said", ",", "you", "'re", "only", "as", "old", "as", "the", "woman", "you", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "I mean, do you feel young ladies keep you feeling young?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "young", "ladies", "keep", "you", "feeling", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I do think -- yes, I think without question, a relationship with somebody younger does keep you alive, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "think", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "think", "without", "question", ",", "a", "relationship", "with", "somebody", "younger", "does", "keep", "you", "alive", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Could you imagine being faithful to her?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "being", "faithful", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I was faithful -- I was married -- my last marriage, which was not successful, I was faithful to it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "faithful", "--", "I", "was", "married", "--", "my", "last", "marriage", ",", "which", "was", "not", "successful", ",", "I", "was", "faithful", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "So you actually are going to be genuine faithful to Crystal?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "actually", "are", "going", "to", "be", "genuine", "faithful", "to", "Crystal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "So what happens to all the other women in the mansion?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "happens", "to", "all", "the", "other", "women", "in", "the", "mansion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "They still come around, every weekend.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "still", "come", "around", ",", "every", "weekend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "But they're not allowed anymore to partake?", "question_tokens": ["But", "they", "'re", "not", "allowed", "anymore", "to", "partake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "They're not allowed upstairs.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "not", "allowed", "upstairs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "So you've hung up your sword, for want of a better phrase?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "hung", "up", "your", "sword", ",", "for", "want", "of", "a", "better", "phrase", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Well, you never know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "never", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "But you honestly believe Hef will not have sex with any other woman ever again other than you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "honestly", "believe", "Hef", "will", "not", "have", "sex", "with", "any", "other", "woman", "ever", "again", "other", "than", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I don't know what to say.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hef"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "So as long as she goes along with it, it's fine?", "question_tokens": ["So", "as", "long", "as", "she", "goes", "along", "with", "it", ",", "it", "'s", "fine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "I mean do you talk about politics much with Hef, I'd imagine?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "talk", "about", "politics", "much", "with", "Hef", ",", "I", "'d", "imagine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No, no, we don't talk about politics.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "talk", "about", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hef"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Do you ever watch that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "watch", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Yes, we watch it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "watch", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "You have?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How am I doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "am", "I", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What other sort of war wounds do you have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "other", "sort", "of", "war", "wounds", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, I have a lower back problem which I got in the wars.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "a", "lower", "back", "problem", "which", "I", "got", "in", "the", "wars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "I suppose, Crystal, when you look at the young Hef, I mean do you kind of wish that you were with him when he was that age?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", ",", "Crystal", ",", "when", "you", "look", "at", "the", "young", "Hef", ",", "I", "mean", "do", "you", "kind", "of", "wish", "that", "you", "were", "with", "him", "when", "he", "was", "that", "age", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I mean, I think he looks great at all ages.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "he", "looks", "great", "at", "all", "ages", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Crystal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "When you see yourself back in those firebrand days?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "yourself", "back", "in", "those", "firebrand", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I wish that we would have met earlier.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wish", "that", "we", "would", "have", "met", "earlier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Essentially, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Essentially", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "So you always try and stay friends with them all?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "always", "try", "and", "stay", "friends", "with", "them", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Have they all taken news of the engagement well, or has there been a little bit of (INAUDIBLE) tension?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "all", "taken", "news", "of", "the", "engagement", "well", ",", "or", "has", "there", "been", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "tension", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Some have been kind --", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "have", "been", "kind", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "DT", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Some tension?", "question_tokens": ["Some", "tension", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Anger and some not quite so kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Anger", "and", "some", "not", "quite", "so", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Who's taken it the worst, Crystal, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "taken", "it", "the", "worst", ",", "Crystal", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Holly -- Holly, OK about it?", "question_tokens": ["Holly", "--", "Holly", ",", "OK", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Holly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Where Holly was, you mean?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "Holly", "was", ",", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Holly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "What was the tally then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "tally", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I don't know what the number was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "number", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Is there anything -- is there anything more important to your life than sex?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "--", "is", "there", "anything", "more", "important", "to", "your", "life", "than", "sex", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Well, I think that perhaps love, friendship.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "perhaps", "love", ",", "friendship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "And how much is you -- I don't want to be personal but how much is your ability to continue having a good sex life down to the wonder drug Viagra?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "much", "is", "you", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "personal", "but", "how", "much", "is", "your", "ability", "to", "continue", "having", "a", "good", "sex", "life", "down", "to", "the", "wonder", "drug", "Viagra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't want to try it without.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "want", "to", "try", "it", "without", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What do you guys talk about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "guys", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "What do you talk about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "talk", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Well, almost everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "almost", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Did you do this?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well, actually, that's a damned good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "damned", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Did you know Marilyn Monroe?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "She was actually on my -- in my brother's acting class in New York,.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "actually", "on", "my", "--", "in", "my", "brother", "'s", "acting", "class", "in", "New", "York", ",", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn Monroe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "She was a remarkable -- Dennis Hopper was in that class too, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["She", "was", "a", "remarkable", "--", "Dennis", "Hopper", "was", "in", "that", "class", "too", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis Hopper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "For you two, when you get married, what will be a classic normal day?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", "two", ",", "when", "you", "get", "married", ",", "what", "will", "be", "a", "classic", "normal", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Well, it's fairly well structured.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "fairly", "well", "structured", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "How much of the \"Playboy\" brand, do you think, is down to you, personally?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "the", "``", "Playboy", "''", "brand", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "is", "down", "to", "you", ",", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Well, I certainly didn't do it alone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "did", "n't", "do", "it", "alone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nebraska"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "You didn't even lose your virginity until you were in your 20s?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "even", "lose", "your", "virginity", "until", "you", "were", "in", "your", "20s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "My parents were very puritan, Nebraska farm people.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "parents", "were", "very", "puritan", ",", "Nebraska", "farm", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What would they have made of the empire you've built?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "they", "have", "made", "of", "the", "empire", "you", "'ve", "built", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well, they were around long enough to see what it was all about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "were", "around", "long", "enough", "to", "see", "what", "it", "was", "all", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "To get it all going?", "question_tokens": ["To", "get", "it", "all", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "She got it all back, many, many times over.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "got", "it", "all", "back", ",", "many", ",", "many", "times", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What did you want to achieve with the brand?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "want", "to", "achieve", "with", "the", "brand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I wanted to create a lifestyle magazine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "create", "a", "lifestyle", "magazine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "He still is, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "still", "is", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 546, "question": "He's always been a bit of a naughty boy, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "always", "been", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "naughty", "boy", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Yeah!", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "It's true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bieber"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Bieber wants to come to the playboy mansion?", "question_tokens": ["Bieber", "wants", "to", "come", "to", "the", "playboy", "mansion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "ARRIS: I have Bieber fever.", "answer_tokens": ["ARRIS", ":", "I", "have", "Bieber", "fever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What's going to happen to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "He'll do all right.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'ll", "do", "all", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Is that the point of these parties?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "point", "of", "these", "parties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I think that's the idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Can people go there and have sex non grata and things?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "people", "go", "there", "and", "have", "sex", "non", "grata", "and", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I've walked in on a couple of people in the game house.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "walked", "in", "on", "a", "couple", "of", "people", "in", "the", "game", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Is this going to be a healthy place for Justin Bieber to find himself?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "going", "to", "be", "a", "healthy", "place", "for", "Justin", "Bieber", "to", "find", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "He's going to bring his father.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "going", "to", "bring", "his", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Do you want to grow up?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "grow", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I think that's the key.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "key", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Cooper, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Cooper", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I mean, it is what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "is", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "But it is a bit weird, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "is", "a", "bit", "weird", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "What's it like being Hugh Hefner's son?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "like", "being", "Hugh", "Hefner", "'s", "son", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I knew you were going to ask that too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "knew", "you", "were", "going", "to", "ask", "that", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Hefner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Am I that predictable?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "that", "predictable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "It's -- again, I don't have anything else to base it off of.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "again", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "anything", "else", "to", "base", "it", "off", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "What kind of dad is he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "dad", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "He's a good dad.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "good", "dad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "How's he done?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "he", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "He's a fantastic son.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "fantastic", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "You must be very popular with your band mates?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "very", "popular", "with", "your", "band", "mates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "A young teenager, maybe?", "question_tokens": ["A", "young", "teenager", ",", "maybe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Could you imagine going into the business?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "going", "into", "the", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "Do you think you will?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "We've talked about it.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "talked", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "I mean, what else do you ask for besides wanting your parents to be happy?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "else", "do", "you", "ask", "for", "besides", "wanting", "your", "parents", "to", "be", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "We have fun.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What is life like in the mansion for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "life", "like", "in", "the", "mansion", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Well, I have a girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "a", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "If you could sum it up in one word, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "sum", "it", "up", "in", "one", "word", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "It's good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Why was it important to you, the Hollywood sign?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "it", "important", "to", "you", ",", "the", "Hollywood", "sign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "I grew very much influenced by the movies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "grew", "very", "much", "influenced", "by", "the", "movies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "How old would you like to see?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "EFNER: There's a song Sinatra did.", "answer_tokens": ["EFNER", ":", "There", "'s", "a", "song", "Sinatra", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "Do you worry about dying?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "dying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "And it's good?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "It's good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Life's pretty good right now?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "'s", "pretty", "good", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Never been better.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "been", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn Monroe"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Of all the pin-ups you've ever had in the history of \"Playboy,\" what's been your personal favorite?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "pin-ups", "you", "'ve", "ever", "had", "in", "the", "history", "of", "``", "Playboy", ",", "''", "what", "'s", "been", "your", "personal", "favorite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "Well, it all began with Marilyn Monroe.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "all", "began", "with", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Would that be your favorite?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "your", "favorite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "It would have to be.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["20th century"]}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Do you think she was the greatest pin up of them all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "was", "the", "greatest", "pin", "up", "of", "them", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "I think she's the major sex star of the 20th century.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "the", "major", "sex", "star", "of", "the", "20th", "century", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "And you bought that picture for 500 dollars and it became a business that's worth -- what are you worth now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "bought", "that", "picture", "for", "500", "dollars", "and", "it", "became", "a", "business", "that", "'s", "worth", "--", "what", "are", "you", "worth", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "I stopped counting a while back.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "stopped", "counting", "a", "while", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["500 dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "Can I guess?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "guess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "But you're north of 100 million dollars, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'re", "north", "of", "100", "million", "dollars", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["100 million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "Or have you been able to adapt to changing dynamics?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "adapt", "to", "changing", "dynamics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "It has to do with adapting.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "to", "do", "with", "adapting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "What would you like you epitaph to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "you", "epitaph", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "As somebody who had some positive impact on changing the social sexual values of his time.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "somebody", "who", "had", "some", "positive", "impact", "on", "changing", "the", "social", "sexual", "values", "of", "his", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "How do you think you'll be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "The same.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "When push comes to shove and you have to assess him as a cultural figure in America, how do you think he'll rate?", "question_tokens": ["When", "push", "comes", "to", "shove", "and", "you", "have", "to", "assess", "him", "as", "a", "cultural", "figure", "in", "America", ",", "how", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'ll", "rate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "I think that he's done incredible things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "'s", "done", "incredible", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]